opas.com 2012-11-09

# International Mail Forwarding - US and Japan Locations - Personal Shoppers Available | OPAS

### Last Updated: October 28, 2011

OPAS is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to the OPAS website and governs data collection and usage. By using the OPAS website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection and Use of Your Personal Information

OPAS collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, and home address in order to provide services to our customers.

OPAS may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from OPAS and its affiliates. OPAS may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

OPAS does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. OPAS may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address) is not transferred to the third party.

OPAS does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

OPAS websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on OPAS or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of OPAS (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of OPAS, or the public.

If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and/or limit your access to the OPAS website.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at service@opas.com.

### Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. OPAS uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. OPAS secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to this Statement

OPAS will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. OPAS encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how OPAS is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date above.

### Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at service@opas. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then contact us at 1-503-262-7036.

### To Unsubscribe From OPAS

You may unsubscribe from OPAS marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the company’s emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe by contacting OPAS 1-503-262-7036.

### Contact Information

OPAS welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that OPAS has not adhered to this Statement, please contact OPAS at service@opas.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. OPAS is located at 6600 NE 78th Ct #A3, Portland OR 97218. We can be reached by phone at 1-503-262-7036.
